[{"answer": "Well, McAuliffe's long history in government I'm not sure what he's talking about.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "I mean that is undeniably true, wasn't it Frank, isn't it?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "He is right.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "I mean he's right, isn't he?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "What can I say...", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Should we care, Frank Rich?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "That's a good question.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Are they anywhere near as judgmental as their parents, and grandparents may be are about this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "ICH: Yeah.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "If that was a one off as he claims, do we really need to get so exercised about it?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "I think there's a big difference as you mentioned earlier.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "What do you think of it?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "I think the problem is that this is what he's saying now, but he's been lying for a long time.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "But is he actually sensible, should he take a back step and get some treatment maybe?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "No comment right now.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "You know there's an allegation that you left this voice mails on Jonathan Martin's voicemail, what do you have to say about those?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Yes I think that I want to say it's a mountain made out of a mole hill.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "I mean, from looking at what the quarterback said, he said that you'd asked a week ago, Jonathan Martin and Mr. Incognito would have been best pals?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "You have to treat it like a workplace.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Should he just choose another sport and get out of it?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "ENEFFEE: Right, you know, it's not just about the physical party.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "I mean, eventually, you're new to the sport in some of the Americans love, right?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "You know, I think that's what we're going to find out.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "If you were in the NFL tomorrow, who do you think you'd rather go to war with in a football sense if you were playing the New York Giants, Richie Incognito, the big beast who destroys all in front of him or Jonathan Martin who runs home to mommy?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "5'11 and three quarters I'd like to say.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "How tall are you Curt?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "I have.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Well you've done a U-turn on nuclear energy so have you (inaudible)?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Well cost, you know, if we start building nuclear power plants like we build solar panels and like we build wind turbines and like we have iPhones and everything else.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "So what has reassured you on those two things?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Well, look I think again, you're going to look at the context.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Well, if I say, Chernobyl or Fukushima or whatever, how do you know that there wasn't going to be more of this if we have allowed more nuclear plants?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Well, those are climate experts they're not people who actually are building power plants and I would say if you talk to people who are building power plants, build particularly solar power plants or wind power plants that they'll tell you a completely different story.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "I sensed there for a lot of experts, Robert Kennedy, is there an inimitability about this?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "The kind of reactors that are advocated for this film by this film are breeder reactors which actually create more plutonium and more weapons grade plutonium.", "docId": "131106pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "If it's so prevalent and so successful?", "qSentId": 491}]